[{"answer": " Come in, Amy.  Please close the door behind you", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Come in, Amy.  Please close the door behind you", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Please, sit down.  Do you know why Ive called this meeting with you", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " No, not really", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Please, sit down.  Do you know why Ive called this meeting with you", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Well, we need to discuss your work performance lately.  A lot of things hav", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": " No, not really", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": "Oh, all right", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Well, we need to discuss your work performance lately.  A lot of things hav", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " First of all, Id like to talk to you about your tardiness.  For the past fe", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Oh, all right", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": "But no one else gets here exactly on time", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 26, "question": " First of all, Id like to talk to you about your tardiness.  For the past fe", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Its true that everyone is late sometimes.  Being late for work every once in ", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 30, "question": "But no one else gets here exactly on time", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " But Im not usually that late.  Only like 30 or 45 minutes late", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Its true that everyone is late sometimes.  Being late for work every once in ", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " That is very late.  Anything over five or ten minutes late is unacceptable.  Yo", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 35, "question": " But Im not usually that late.  Only like 30 or 45 minutes late", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " No, Ive just been having insomnia.  Its making it difficult for me to get up in th", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 40, "question": " That is very late.  Anything over five or ten minutes late is unacceptable.  Yo", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Well, Im afraid thats not an acceptable excuse.  Youve got to start comin", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 44, "question": " No, Ive just been having insomnia.  Its making it difficult for me to get up in th", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " OK.  I understand", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Well, Im afraid thats not an acceptable excuse.  Youve got to start comin", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Good.  Now, lets talk about the projects youve been working on lately", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 49, "question": " OK.  I understand", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Good.  Now, lets talk about the projects youve been working on lately", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " The last project report you turned in was two weeks late and I must say that i", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 51, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": "I just had a lot of projects going on and I couldnt finish it in time", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 55, "question": " The last project report you turned in was two weeks late and I must say that i", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": "If you were not going to finish on time, you should have let me know.  Tha", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 56, "question": "I just had a lot of projects going on and I couldnt finish it in time", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Im sorry.  I should have talked to you", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 61, "question": "If you were not going to finish on time, you should have let me know.  Tha", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Im afraid sorry doesnt fix the problem, Amy.  This isnt the first time this ha", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Im sorry.  I should have talked to you", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Im sorry for that too.  I think the lack of sleep is affecting my performance a", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Im afraid sorry doesnt fix the problem, Amy.  This isnt the first time this ha", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Im sorry youre having problems sleeping, but we cant accept that as a", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Im sorry for that too.  I think the lack of sleep is affecting my performance a", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " No, I will try to fix it", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Im sorry youre having problems sleeping, but we cant accept that as a", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Good.  Now please take what I am saying seriously.  You can consider thi", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 77, "question": " No, I will try to fix it", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Yes, I understand", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Good.  Now please take what I am saying seriously.  You can consider thi", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Im glad.  Youve been a great employee in the past and wed hate to los", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Yes, I understand", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Thank you.  Youll see improvement, I promise", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Im glad.  Youve been a great employee in the past and wed hate to los", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " I hope so.  OK, thats all for now", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Thank you.  Youll see improvement, I promise", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " OK.  Bye", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I hope so.  OK, thats all for now", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "03-05", "aSentId": 90, "question": " OK.  Bye", "qSentId": 89}]
